["Love the Way" playing]
[woman imitating drumroll] Ta-da!
The Amur Adonis buds
have finally sprouted.
- [man 1] Lift that up a bit more.
- [woman laughs]
Today marks a momentous day as life has
once again sprouted from this red soil.
Okay, I guess it technically didn't sprout
from the soil.
[man 1] Santa's unaffected by gravity.
[man 2] Uh, that's debatable.
I say Santa's affected by the gravity,
but Rudolph and the sleigh aren't.
Aren't you guys putting
too much effort into this?
I wish you had that level of enthusiasm
for analyzing soil samples.
[man 2] Seriously?
Ji-young, another video journal
to your daughter, hmm?
Hi, Nan-young.
I heard you got another rotten tooth.
The news of that even reached Mars.
- [panicked talking]
- [woman 2] Stay calm!
Head to the emergency exit!
- [man 2] Hurry!
- [woman 2] Ji-young!
[dramatic sting]
[radio crackles]
HQ? Joo here.
I'm in the habitat module now.
[NASA officer] Copy.
Proceed slowly and steadily.
- Your pace is good.
- Heading towards ISRU for supplies.
[beeping]
[rustling]
[grunts]
Suit, display
the oxygen generator location.
[breathing heavily]
[metal creaking]
[grunting]
Oxygen tank secured.
[grunts]
Initiating recharge.
[intriguing music playing]
[grunts]
[dramatic sting]
[surreal music playing]
[music builds]
[heavy breathing]
[NASA officer] Nan-young,
what's the holdup?
- Recharge now.
- [Nan-young gasping]
- [breathing heavily, gasps]
- [oxygen hisses]
- [researcher 1] Nailed it!
- [researcher 2] Done.
[researcher 1] She's practically built
for Mars missions.
- [researcher 2] All right. That's a wrap.
- [researcher 1] I know!
Without that tiny stall,
it would've been a record.
- Why'd you stop?
- [Nan-young] I thought I saw something.
Really? I'll look at it.
- Ready to call it a day?
- Yep. Let's get out of here.
[man] Oh, Sam, by the way,
the engineers requested a meeting
about the rotation axis issue
from the last gravity test.
I cannot accept this decision.
There were no issues with my test results.
The bereaved families
received their belongings,
and as you can imagine,
old wounds are reopening.
You're the only member of
the Mars Expedition crew
who lost someone.
It's just too cruel for you to visit
the accident site
during this mission.
[Nan-young scoffs]
You know what's really cruel, Captain?
You know how much work I put into this.
I swear, I'm not affected.
You're really not affected?
[sighs] That's exactly the problem.
See, Nan-young, that's not
a normal psychological response.
The doctor expressed concerns
about that aspect of your psyche.
Stand by as a backup for now.
Why don't you have a little break
in Korea? Clear your head.
[reporter] Breaking news.
As the astronaut selection process
for the upcoming fourth Mars expedition
has officially begun,
NASA is now able to share more details
about the mission.
Twenty-four years ago,
a large tremor on the surface of Mars
caused the collapse of
an underground manned research facility.
All crew members of the second Mars
expedition were lost in this tragedy.
The incident was devastating,
not only for the families of the lost crew
but also for the people of the world
who had collectively hoped
for their safe return.
The belongings of the late Son Ji-young,
the first Korean astronaut selected
for a Mars expedition,
will be among the items brought back
from the red planet.
[poignant music playing]
[quirky music playing]
[announcer] Seoul Station Square
and surrounding zones
are approved for low-flying drones.
Air taxi drivers are advised to exercise
caution and avoid drone collisions.
Once again…
[sighs]
[mellow music plays]
- [sighs]
- [ringtone]
- [Rosa] Hey, Nans! Did you get home safe?
- You scared me!
- [Rosa] How are you feeling?
- How am I feeling?
Oh, I feel like I'm watching my dreams
crumble before my eyes.
[Rosa] Aw.
Come on. Let me see your face.
Turn on your camera.
- Fine. Here's my crestfallen face.
- [Rosa] Hmm.
[Rosa laughs]
Whoa! What, do you live
in some antique store?
Where did you get it all?
It's Mom and Dad's.
Uh, I really need to go through it all
one of these days.
Oh my gosh. This is so dang cute!
Hey!
- Quit walking through me!
- [detector] Scanning.
[Rosa] Excuse you!
- [Nan-young] Stop getting in my way.
- [detector] Target. Managing mode.
- [grunts] Move it.
- Whoa! Hey! Hey! [Groans]
- [giggles]
- [detector trills]
[gasps]
[Rosa] Whoa!
- Hey!
- Bye, Nans. Talk soon!
- [Nan-young moans]
- [detector beeping]
[quirky music playing]
LOST IN STARLIGHT
MARS EXPEDITION TEAM'S BELONGINGS RETURN
AFTER 25 YEARS
MODERN ELECTRONICS REPAIRS
[both gasp]
[cries out]
[gasps]
[music builds, ends]
[both gasp]
- [man] Oh, I'm so sorry. Are you okay?
- [Nan-young gasps]
[breathing heavily]
- That was totally my fault.
- [beeping]
[man on smart watch] Hey, hurry it up
and get over here. [Laughs]
Oh boy, look at him. Ah.
Oh, I'm late.
[Nan-young] Uh, you should get going.
Huh?
[Nan-young] Oh…
The Crozley All-in-one 2023 edition?
I can, uh, repair that for you. [Chuckles]
- Uh...
- Here's my card. Bring it by.
I'll fix it for you.
- So sorry!
- Wait! Uh…
- That one's for unit 402.
- 402?
Just send it up there.
They'll figure it out.
- Right. Have a good day.
- [Nan-young] Hmm.
[whirring]
[man panting]
[people chattering]
[man] Ah, come on.
I just had it a second ago. Where did it...
- ♪ I've been looking for love…  ♪
- Huh.
[man] I know I had
the soldering iron right here.
Ah, there it is.
Let's have a look now, shall we?
Huh.
[woman] I brought this to you
over a month ago,
and you're just now taking a look at it?
[man] Well, see, Jay said
that he had already finished it...
[woman] Indispensable employee, isn't he?
Without him, there'd be no one
to pin the blame on.
All right. I'm working. Don't distract me.
[Nan-young grunts]
So…
There is a young guy
that works here, right?
- Young guy?
- [Nan-young] Yeah.
Hmm. Oh, Jay.
Hey, Jay.
- [Jay] Oh, you came.
- Oh, Jay!
- Who's she?
- Girlfriend?
Oh, uh. Come on, Miss Oh.
- I, uh…
- [Miss Oh laughs]
She's a customer.
- [Miss Oh] Goodness, me.
- [man] Oh, to be young again…
- Pipe down.
- [Miss Oh] Time of your life.
- [Jay] Do you want me to load them?
- Ah, you take care of your customer.
- Okay.
- Nice work, Jay.
Thank you, Miss Oh.
Uh, follow me.
- Uh, this way.
- [Nan-young] Mm.
Glad you were able to find the place okay.
I was worried you might not
since I rushed off.
- Come on up.
- Oh, sure.
- Hmm.
- [Jay sighs]
SEWOON PLAZA
[piano music playing]
Uh…
Hmm.
The board right here is smashed.
Yeah, thanks to you.
I doubt it was in working condition
before it took that little tumble.
- [Nan-young] Mm-mm.
- [Jay] Hmm.
So, do you really think you can fix it?
Well, I'll try to start sourcing
the parts.
Between my connections
and the fact this is a budget retro item,
shouldn't take long.
Hmm?
Can I get your name and number?
[Nan-young] Uh.
- Hmm.
I'll give you a call
as soon as it's ready.
- Here.
- [Nan-young] Uh…
[Jay] You click it.
Oh.
JOO NAN-YOUNG
[Rosa] With a pen? On paper?
Wow. Those guys still exist?
Hey! This is a perfect opportunity
to clear your head.
You should set up a date.
Chill.
How are things going at the lab?
And with the board?
[Rosa] Mm.
Well, your psych test scores
have barely made the cut,
but you can probably make it up elsewhere.
Look at this.
Rosa, what did you find for me?
You can see
they've encountered some issues
with the atomic battery
on the life detector.
Let's see.
I need to get it from 270 to 300?
It's obvious the team
has really been struggling since you left.
Hmm.
Okay.
I gotta stay on top of my game.
Inspiration might strike at any moment,
you know?
DR. JOO NAN-YOUNG DEMOTED TO BACKUP
Absolutely. Let me know if you find
anything in similar condition.
- [merchant] Will do. Later.
- We'll be on our way. Thanks!
I'm gonna sit as far from the teachers
as I can.
[boy] You were up all night practicing?
Don't tell me you've given up
on music completely.
You wanna end up like me?
[Jay scoffs] Come on now.
What would be so bad
about ending up like you?
[Jay's boss] Uh, you're nuts,
you know that?
[Jay] Oh.
Oh!
DR. JOO NAN-YOUNG
Wait. She's a famous person?
[Jay's boss] What's grabbed
your attention now?
[Jay chuckles]
I'm so impressed.
Hmm.
["Life Goes On" playing]
[sighs]
Do we have the noise test results yet?
[researcher] I'm out of here
for the night.
♪ I wake up from my bed ♪
♪ Just to find it was a dream  ♪
♪ Is it my darkest fear?  ♪
♪ No one will be there for me  ♪
♪ I do know  ♪
- [song continues in Korean]
- Look!
- [zapping]
- Oh!
Nan-young here.
To address your concerns
and demonstrate my readiness,
I've continued working on upgrading
the performance
of the life-form detector
since returning home.
The research
has been progressing smoothly,
and I am on track to reach 300
prior to launch.
If so, I am hopeful
that you will consider allowing me
to lead the upcoming Mars expedition.
[sighs]
[watch dings]
[song fades]
[Jay] Good news!
I think I have a solution.
Can we meet tomorrow?
[repairman] Oh dear, well…
Looks like it's not a fit after all.
- Sorry for making you waste a trip.
- [Jay] Uh…
No problem.
Thanks for having a look at it.
- [Jay sighs]
- Come on, just give it back.
Ugh. I don't want to be a bother.
It's not that important anyway.
- It's not even mine.
- Huh? What?
But here. Scribbled right on the front.
"Nan-young."
That's not you?
It is, but…
It was my mom's.
[Jay] Well, then.
All the more reason to fix it.
[Nan-young grunts]
Listen, sir. I understand
you've already put a lot of work into it,
but really, it's not a big deal.
Um…
You don't have to call me "sir." Just Jay.
Huh?
It's my name.
Call me Jay.
Okay then, Jay. [Laughs]
- Well, thanks but... [gasps]
- I know!
I've worked up quite the appetite.
What do you say? Wanna grab a bite?
[Jay chuckles]
[sighs]
[slurps] Oh!
Never tastes this good
when I make it at home.
They say food tastes better
when you're not the chef.
But then again,
they also say food tastes better
when enjoyed with… friends?
- Oh, we're friends?
- [Jay chuckles]
Just a turn of phrase, you know?
Let me get the check.
- It's the least I can do for you, sir.
- Come on now.
Enough with the "sir." It's Jay.
Let's just use our first names.
After all, we have to see each other
three times
so we can fix this bad boy. Right?
- [Nan-young sighs] Then…
- Oh.
Call me by my name the third time.
[Jay] Oh, uh… don't be a stranger.
Huh.
Hmm.
[thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
Huh?
[sighs]
- [horn honking]
- [exclaims]
Uh!
[grunting]
[panting]
Huh?
Nan-young.
Uh-huh?
[whimsical music playing]
[exhales]
[sighs]
- Uh.
- Oh.
Oh.
Well, this is our…
Third time… meeting so…
I can call you…
[exhales]
…by your name now, right?
[Nan-young murmurs]
[Jay pants]
- Let me catch my breath.
- [Nan-young laughs]
[both laugh]
[music continues]
- [Nan-young] Come on. Let's go.
- Okay. Here.
How did you know
I didn't have an umbrella?
You weren't carrying one earlier,
so I ran to catch up with you.
[Nan-young laughs]
[music fades]
This is the model
that was released right after yours,
but the specs and design
are basically the same.
[Nan-young] Hmm.
It wasn't exactly easy to get my hands on,
but with my connections,
I was able to get it for pretty cheap.
They look just about the same, don't they?
What do you think?
- It plays music?
- Of course.
Let's put something on.
Just a sec.
Hmm.
[watch chimes]
[watch voice] Bluetooth device connected.
Huh?
We've got a functioning turntable,
and you're using it
as a Bluetooth speaker?
So trapped in the modern age.
[mellow music begins]
Uh…
Oh.
[sighs]
My favorite song.
I found it on cloud a few years ago
and was hooked.
I think it's a demo of some kind.
Seems unfinished.
♪ I lose myself to fun… ♪
[Jay breathes shakily] Oh.
I played this song over and over
while studying.
My roommate couldn't take it
and moved out.
[laughs] Funny, right?
- [Jay] I can't believe it.
- Huh?
[gasps] Do you know this track?
- [Jay clears throat]
- [Nan-young laughs] That's wild!
I've never met anyone else
who knows this song.
Hmm. Yeah, it's wild.
I deleted it right after posting.
I never thought anyone
would actually hear it.
Huh?
This is your song?
As in, you sang it?
- You're lying! [Gasps]
- [bang]
[Jay's boss] Our Jay here?
He never lies, I tell you.
Oh, come on! Right now?
I got no customers up there.
My part-timer is slacking off as usual.
- Hey, I'm not slacking off.
- All in my way again.
My guitar! Hey!
- Sorry.
- [Jay] Oh!
Stop using this space for naps! Ugh.
[tuning guitar]
Actually…
It's still… pretty unfinished.
Sure you wanna hear it?
Uh, mm-hmm.
[clears throat]
[sighs]
[strums guitar, stops]
[exhales, strums guitar, stops]
Three, four…
♪ I lose myself to fun  ♪
♪ In nameless cities  ♪
♪ Drifting to the unknown ♪
♪ Sleeping somewhere in between ♪
♪ For someone like me
Life is sometimes just hard to foresee  ♪
♪ Holding my breath
I'll step through concrete mountains  ♪
♪ I'll overcome it all
And wipe the dust off my face  ♪
[stops playing, sighs]
So, it's true.
It really is your song, isn't it?
Uh…
Are you a solo artist? Or is there a band?
Do you perform live on stage as well?
- That's a lot of questions.
- Well, I've been so curious!
I looked, but I couldn't find anything.
No albums, no social media at all.
God, I love that song. I can't believe it.
[gasps] I'm honored!
- [groans] I said, "I'm honored."
- [guitar music playing]
[Nan-young groans]
[beeping]
SPACE EXPLORATION
DR. JOO'S DREAM TO BLOOM FLOWERS ON MARS
MARS EXPLORATION INTERVIEW
AIRS AT THIS TIME TOMORROW
[music fades]
["Love the Way" playing]
[man] Let's have a look.
Potassium and phosphoric acid levels are…
Why, they're… just far too high.
Just what was everyone doing that
they let it get this bad this quickly?
Huh?
Let's see here.
[man singing along to song]
♪ I love your way  ♪
♪ Hold me before the dark  ♪
Hmm. And where did all the sprouts
from the germination room go?
Huh…
Hey, Dad. I'm here.
- Hmm. Hmm.
- [song continues playing]
[sighs]
Hmm.
- [Nan-young sighs]
- [beeping]
♪ I love your way… ♪
[beeping continues]
[reporter] Thanks to a social media post
by the Korean Space Agency,
the public has finally caught a glimpse
of the life detection device
you've been developing.
What are the chances it will encounter
real Martians during the expedition?
[Nan-young exhales]
The life-forms we are hoping to find
are generally microorganisms,
or more specifically, we are looking for
traces of organic matter
that is emitted by microorganisms
via respiration.
Wow! That sounds fascinating, Dr. Joo.
So you're saying
that the Martians we might meet
will be microorganisms, right?
[Nan-young and others laugh]
Yes, we might just.
[reporter] I admit, this next question
might be a bit sensitive.
Your mother was the late Son Ji-young,
one of the astronauts who passed away
during a previous expedition to Mars.
I'm sure many of our viewers
also remember her as well.
How and why did you decide to pursue
being not just an astronaut
but a Martian explorer?
- Oh, well, uh… uh… to be honest…
- [sound distortion]
I… I don't really remember much about her.
[poignant music playing]
Uh…
MOM'S ON MARS
MOM ISN'T ON MARS
[high-pitched ringing]
[music intensifies, recedes]
- [panelist] Dr. Joo?
- [gasps]
Yes. [Exhales] Sorry about that.
[reporter] I admit, this next question
might be a bit sensitive.
Your mother was the late Son Ji-young,
one of the astronauts who passed away
during a previous expedition to Mars.
I'm sure many of our viewers
also remember her as well.
How and why did you decide to pursue
being not just an astronaut
but a Martian explorer?
[music continues]
[sighs]
[watch dings]
RECORD PLAYER: IT'S RAINING…
LET'S GET SOME OF THIS
- [Jay groans] I'm stuffed.
- [Nan-young] Tell me about it.
Nothing like a tasty meal to cheer you up
when you're feeling down.
[Jay] Hmm.
Yeah, uh, when you're feeling down,
you could, uh…
you could always talk to me about it.
- Hmm?
- Of course you don't have to.
[awkward chuckle]
Hmm.
Well, then, do you mind
if I ask you something?
[Jay] Fire away.
So… how did you get into music?
- Oh. Wow.
- [both chuckle]
It's, uh… hmm…
It's not too exciting, I'm afraid.
- [Nan-young chuckles]
- [Jay] Hmm.
When I was growing up,
I was basically raised
by my grandfather in the countryside.
I had to go with him
to the public bathhouse.
He'd scrub me with this awful brush.
I hated it.
And I let everyone know too.
Whenever he'd take me to the baths,
I'd cry and cry, calling out for my mom.
He taught me to sing
so that I wouldn't cry.
He told me he'd buy me a Coke
if I didn't cry.
Simple enough.
[both laugh]
Aw, sweet little baby Jay.
Must have been cute!
I was cute as a button.
- [laughs]
- Grown-up Jay turned out even better.
- Pretty handsome.
- Okay.
- Uh-oh. You stay here.
- Huh?
- I'll go get us some more.
- Oh.
I'll go too. Don't want this cutie pie
getting kidnapped.
[both laugh]
[Jay] All right, all right.
[chuckles, sighs]
What's grown-up Jay thinking now?
I guess he's probably…
He's probably just waiting.
Waiting for his desire to sing
to come back to him.
Hmm.
[gentle music playing]
[Nan-young] Hmm.
There. Now it's back.
[music fades]
When I was a little girl,
my father would take me stargazing.
I always wondered
what could be out there in space.
And he would just go on and on
about Mars this, Mars that.
[laughs] You could call it brainwashing.
So then we have your father to thank
for your Mars obsession?
[laughs] Sure do.
I guess I wanted to be someone special.
One of the few people on Earth
who get to go to Mars.
- Pretty special.
- Hmm.
- Nan-young.
- Hmm?
You're already special.
Doesn't matter to me
if you're up there or down here.
- I know what you're trying to do.
- [Jay] What?
All those compliments. Hmm.
[Jay laughs]
I should tell you now.
Just so you know, it won't work.
Because one day,
I might just fly off into space.
Maybe, but for now…
Huh?
…you're a backup, right?
[chuckles]
- [Nan-young grunts]
- [Jay] Huh?
Still, we can't.
["Purple Stereo" playing]
[cries out] I can't! No commitments!
Eyes on the prize! Ugh.
[laughs]
What commitment?
- Stay away.
- Huh?
[laughs]
- Let's keep our distance.
- Distance?
- Uh.
- Hmm.
[Nan-young] Mm.
- [Jay laughs]
- Don't!
[both laugh]
[man] Hey! What's all the racket
down there?
What? Do you think you own the place, huh?
- Sorry! Sorry! Sorry!
- Sorry! Sorry!
[both laugh]
♪ Ashes to our love… ♪
[Nan-young] Come on, come on!
[both laugh]
♪ We've always been here ♪
[laughing heartily]
♪ We running on the stereo ♪
- [Jay yells]
- [Nan-young yells, laughs]
♪ Always been here… ♪
[Jay] Oh…
Are you okay? Oh dear.
- [Nan-young laughs]
- Oh boy.
I'm so sorry. Sorry about that.
[both laugh]
♪ Staying still here ♪
Here, let me see.
♪ We whisper under purple glow ♪
[both panting]
It's complicated, Jay.
What is?
[both breathing heavily]
[Nan-young moans]
[elevator whirring]
♪ We've always been here ♪
♪ We running on the stereo ♪
♪ Always been here ♪
♪ We wonder why we found the love ♪
♪ A lot of melodies ♪
♪ I love your fingers
Playing sounds of Billie ♪
♪ Purple romance ♪
♪ The glowing ♪
♪ It's a favorite scene for you and me ♪
♪ We dancing on the stereo
The one last ♪
♪ The one last time ♪
♪ We've always been here ♪
♪ We running on the stereo ♪
♪ Always been here ♪
[song ends]
Ah! Do you ever sleep?
Yeah, I feel like I'm so close,
but I just can't work this out!
Layers A and B with a mesh weave,
then B and C on top.
Ugh, that's already too thick. [Groans]
[sighs] I need to finish this,
so someone can take it to Mars.
[yawns]
Just a sec.
- That someone is me, isn't it? Am I wrong?
- [yawns]
- Joo Nan-young.
- Hmm?
If you want me to go, you're gonna have
to tell me to my natjjak.
Practicing Korean?
[Rosa] I'm getting better thanks to you,
but I'll be sure to master it
once I start dating.
- Oh, Rosa.
- [Rosa laughs]
You're gonna miss out on dating on Mars.
Speaking of which, how's it going
for you and that artist guy?
- [watch dings]
- [Rosa] Huh?
Oh, speak of the devil.
This is him, right? It's him! [Laughs]
- Hello? You must be the man…
- Rosa!
…that Nan-young's been mooning over.
She's totally in love.
- Cut it out, Rosa!
- [Rosa laughs]
He… hello? Hey, Jay.
Outside? Now?
Huh?
[drone whirring]
LET'S CELEBRATE! HAPPY BIRTHDAY, MARS GEEK
[chuckles]
[laughs heartily]
[both laugh]
[creaking]
Hmm.
That should work.
[Nan-young] I told you, didn't I?
He's a certified Mars fanatic.
He's got quite the setup.
Like an undercover Earth warrior spy.
[Nan-young chuckles]
He's transmitting to space right now.
He thinks someone on Mars
wants to wish me a very happy birthday.
[Jay] So then, he's sending a message
to your mom, huh?
- Uh, how did you know?
- Sorry.
When your girlfriend's famous,
a web search brings up
more than her birthday.
[sighs]
Now you know
that he's trying to reach my mother.
And has been doing so
for the last 20 years.
I don't think he believes she's gone.
[Jay sighs]
It's a birthday tradition to come here
and send a message off to Mars.
Well, then, from here on out,
you can count me in too.
[father] Okay, the transmission
has been engaged.
I know it looks small,
but it's really rather effective.
Do you mind if I take a look with you?
Not at all. Here, you take the driver...
[exclaims]
[both exclaiming]
[both apologizing]
Don't think you can call yourself
a repairman.
[laughs] You're more like
a destruction man.
[father] This isn't small at all.
This side is completely destroyed.
[Jay] Is this little signal really enough?
Can it make it all the way to Mars?
Radio waves can go anywhere,
but someone has to be there
to receive them.
Hmm… Once the antenna
at the base is completed,
we'll be able to make live calls.
Well, with a 20-minute delay.
- [Jay] Listen, Nan-young.
- Hmm?
If you do end up being chosen
to go to Mars,
how will I contact you?
By… walkie-talkie?
[laughs] Jay!
- [both laugh]
- [Nan-young sighs]
Do you think…
That I'll get to go to space? To Mars?
We could go right now.
- [Nan-young] Hmm?
- Together.
- Huh.
- [piano music playing]
[Nan-young] That one. Yeah, look.
- [Jay] This one?
- It's so cute.
Ooh, here it comes.
It's dropping now! Wow!
- [Jay] Looks so tasty!
- [Nan-young] Sure does!
[Jay] I've never been to an observatory.
- I can't remember the last time. Whoa!
- Whoa!
- What's that constellation?
- I'm not sure.
[Nan-young chuckles]
[Jay gasps]
Jay, there it is. That's Mars.
- Where? Which one?
- Right there.
Oh! Doesn't seem that far at all, huh?
[Nan-young] I told you.
Spatially speaking, it's very close.
[Jay] But it takes six months
to get there.
[Nan-young] Ah, six months
is nothing in space.
[young Nan-young] Wow.
It doesn't look that far.
It's so close, right?
You'll be back home soon.
- [chuckles]
- [sighs]
Isn't that right, Mom? [Laughs]
[both cry out]
Why did you lie to me, Mommy?
You lied to me!
You said that you'd be back soon.
Why did you lie to me?
[yelling]
[young Nan-young] I miss my mommy.
[Nan-young crying out]
[young Nan-young] Get her back for me!
I miss her.
Don't go!
I love you too, Mommy.
- [echoing] Liar.
- [gasps]
Nan-young,
do you want rice or toast with...
Oh. What's the matter?
Why are you crying?
- Oh.
- [sobbing] It's nothing.
It's just a dream.
Nightmares, they say…
Are vanquished by the morning sunshine.
Huh? Oh.
Is this a greenhouse?
I didn't know
that you were into gardening.
Uh, not earth gardening anyway.
- [beeps]
- [Jay] Oh. Whoa. Ooh.
Who's this guy?
It's a detector that can find even
the tiniest traces of micro organic life.
The culmination of my hard work.
That's him.
- Right?
- [Jay laughs]
Wow. I have no idea what
you're talking about, but it's incredible.
- Hey, it is!
- [Jay laughs]
Of course it is. You made it.
[detector trills]
- Amur Adonis.
- Whoa.
They're unique
because they bloom in the snow.
When they bloom,
they give off a small amount of heat.
These samples have been engineered
to maximize self-heating.
And with them, we're going to make
a flower garden on Mars.
These will be like the protective parents.
Here you go.
[detector beeps]
They look pretty safe in there.
What, with a fancy beam projector
and armored greenhouse.
[Nan-young laughs]
- You weren't listening at all, were you?
- [Jay laughs]
Dr. Joo, I do need to buckle down
and study more.
Today's practical experiment will involve
the self-heating capabilities of Jay,
engineered to protect Joo Nan-young.
Get away from me!
[both laugh]
[Nan-young] I guess I must have been
about five or so.
I made an astronaut like this one
with art supplies.
Seems like
you've been thinking about space
since before you started walking.
Oh, I just realized that little astronaut
made it to space before I did.
- Hmm.
- How is that?
My mom took him.
Since I obviously couldn't go along,
she took him in my place.
I remember how I collected candy wrappers
for what seemed like months
so that I could make his suit shiny.
That's amazing, you know?
That you can remember those details
from your childhood.
[Nan-young] It's weird, right?
I remember all that,
but sometimes I forget how she looked.
Candy wrappers…
As C and D.
Scotch tape for B.
- Popsicle stick as A.
- [Jay] Hmm.
[Nan-young gasps]
A on its own!
If A is an independent material,
it should work!
What… what are you talking... Ah!
Whoa. What's going on?
If A is laid out independently,
then B can be laid between C and D.
[beeping]
[Nan-young gasps]
Eureka!
[detector] Scanning.
There are a few functions
that need to be tweaked and fine-tuned.
- [chuckles]
- Scanning target.
But even in its current state,
the sensitivity and speed are perfect.
Good work.
[woman] Nicely done, Dr. Joo. Great work!
[deputy director] Microorganisms.
In the clean room!
Who was on sterilization duty?
[chuckles]
[jazzy music playing]
[Nan-young] I have earned
another one of these.
And you?
Just another Coke?
I just made a groundbreaking discovery!
Dinner is my treat.
Mmm. Coke is fine.
[band tuning instruments]
They're gonna play a show.
[band starts to play]
♪ A sea of stars ♪
♪ Where everything sparkles
The way they do ♪
♪ Are you here to tell you mattered… ♪
Wow.
It's nice.
[chuckles softly]
[people chattering]
No. Yeah, I saw them last week too,
and they were amazing. So good.
Jay.
Hey.
You're not answering my messages.
There isn't anything for us to talk about.
[woman] Whatever.
Just keep running away, Jay.
[Jay exhales angrily]
You know, a lot of people out there
still like your music.
My music?
Yes, that's my music.
- And you're using it for yourself.
- Our next show.
- Jay. Oh.
- The Panda Sound team is coming.
You know, that label you love so much?
- Uh. I'm sorry. Let's go.
- [Nan-young] Uh, okay.
[woman] Saturday. Rolling Burn.
We go on at eight.
You should come too.
Jay's pretty impressive
when he plays live.
Hmm. She's just an old band mate.
But we're not friends anymore.
Sorry about that.
[sighs] It's all right.
But I would like to see it.
You on stage.
I tried looking it up,
but there's nothing.
Hmm. Do you have any videos of it?
Hmm?
- Hmm.
- [beep]
[Jay] Di-a! Di-a! Look over here. Di-a.
Cut it out!
Stop recording, or I'll kill you!
[crowd cheering]
[guitar riff plays]
[tense music playing]
[guitar riff continues]
[music fades]
[Di-a] What's wrong? You don't like it?
I think it started to fall a little flat.
So I tweaked it a bit.
Made it better for live performance.
[Jay chuckles angrily]
You haven't changed at all, have you?
I… it barely sounds like my song,
and the chorus lyrics…
[scoffs]
Since you can't sing it,
it never would have seen the light of day.
You should be happy
someone wants to sing it at all.
Just forget it. I don't know why
I should expect anything else.
Good luck without a guitarist.
The tone in your voice
made me think you might've changed.
[Di-a] If you leave now, well,
then whatever this is
will be your life forever.
You won't get another chance, Jay.
One last shot
to make up for all your mistakes.
- [crowd cheering]
- [muffled music playing]
- [man] Hold up. Are you back?
- [Jay] Huh?
Come on, join us. Let's put on a show!
[crowd cheering]
[muffled music playing in background]
[tapping microphone]
- [Di-a sighs]
- [crowd cheers]
[Di-a] We're on the last song already?
[man] Over here, over here!
We've got a surprise band member
joining us.
- I think you all remember him, don't you?
- [crowd yelling] Yeah!
On guitar, Jay!
[clapping]
- [Di-a laughs]
- [crowd] Jay!
[Di-a] And on that note…
We've got a new song for you all tonight,
something special from The Moles.
Written by him.
"Stay."
[crowd cheering]
[mellow guitar music playing]
[clears throat]
[Jay] Hyung, you should come in
right here.
Mmm.
I'll send this version to the label.
Um… uh…
You went and changed everything around,
and now it's a mess.
- Wait!
- How do you expect me to feel?
The show's starting.
Get on stage now, Jay!
[Jay] I can't! I can't do it anymore!
[Di-a] Nobody cares
about your stupid story.
GARBAGE
JUST A DIARY
[Jay gasping]
[Di-a vocalizing]
♪ Somewhere higher than the clouds ♪
♪ We're dancing with the lights ♪
♪ Baby, don't let go ♪
♪ Stay with me ♪
♪ Like the fairy tales we used to… ♪
[gasps]
He's amazing! Jay!
[laughing joyfully]
Huh?
[Nan-young] Jay,
you really won't sing anymore?
[Jay] Hmm.
I don't know. Even if I rejoin,
Di-a is the singer of the band.
And to be fair,
I don't know if I want to rejoin.
Really? Hmm.
I know I'm not a musician,
but that song, you know.
Your song, I like Jay's version more.
And of course
your performance tonight was impressive.
I just hope there comes a day
when everyone else in the world
can hear your beautiful voice,
and it's not just me.
You don't like private concerts?
Not when I have
such an amazing man to show off.
- [watch dings]
- [Jay chuckles]
Uh.
[gasps]
I made it!
- [Jay] Huh?
- [Nan-young squeals]
- [Jay] What is it? What's going on, huh?
- [Nan-young] It's a secret.
Just celebrate with me, okay?
[Jay chuckles]
[Jay's boss] First you said
you'd never sell it.
Now you're harvesting the thing for parts?
Looks like you've got
something to live for.
Yep. Life's as sweet as it can be.
[chuckles]
Well, all right then.
[siren wailing in the distance]
It hasn't officially been announced yet,
but the team found something
near the lava zone.
A collision crater by sector 6F.
There is a possibility
that the collision crater
contains organic material.
So, if you bring
the life-form detection system,
there'll be a lot work for you
on the mission.
It would be a shame to miss the chance
to discover this amount of data
while we're on Mars.
Thank you.
I'll sleep well tonight, Captain.
It's a bit of a tight schedule,
but send out your last words video
by 0600.
Wrap things up ASAP and return.
- Can you do that?
- Yes, sir.
JAY
[dance music playing]
- Make a wish!
- [Nan-young laughs]
Hey, Chief. The official announcement
doesn't air till tomorrow, right?
That's right. 8 p.m.
No blabbing before then.
[everyone exclaiming and laughing]
Chief, doesn't the announcement
air tonight?
Huh? Dr. Joo! It's on tonight!
- [laughing]
- In two years, I'll be patient.
[Nan-young] All right then.
Before I go, okay?
- [researcher] I'm so happy for you!
- [Nan-young] Cheers!
[door opens]
[lights chime]
Hmm.
- [mellow music playing]
- Hmm.
Oh, Nan-young.
I can see you've been pretty busy.
[grunts]
[humming]
[chuckles]
Where's her vinyl?
Frank Sinatra and Chet Baker?
Huh.
Oh.
Alice Mae King's hit, "Love the Way."
Her mom had a taste for the classics.
Oh!
Hmm. [Sighs]
Oh… a QR code?
Hmm.
[beeps]
[Ji-young] Day 49 on Mars, 9:47 p.m.
The winds calmed down today,
so it was rather mild.
The weather has been
really agreeable lately, so I feel great.
- And I have a surprise for you.
- ["Love the Way" playing]
[imitating drumroll] Ta-da!
The Amur Adonis buds
have finally sprouted.
[chuckling]
Today marks a momentous day
as life has once again sprouted
from this red soil.
Okay, I guess it didn't sprout
from the soil.
Ji-young, another video journal
to your daughter, hmm?
Mm-hmm.
Hi, Nan-young.
I heard you got another rotten tooth.
The news of that even reached Mars.
You have to brush your teeth properly
to become an astronaut.
- [Ji-young laughs]
- Doo-doo-doo.
Do we have a tooth-brushing regulation?
Shush! Just tell her that we have one.
[laughs]
All right. She's right.
You have too many cavities, missy.
Don't forget to brush your teeth
before bed.
And listen to everything your father says.
And eat lots and lots of veggies too!
Don't forget your English studies.
Good night, my darling.
See you in your dreams, hon.
Your mom will haunt your dreams
if you don't brush your teeth!
- Just like how she haunts everyone here.
- Okay. Enough, you guys.
- [rumbling]
- [alarm sounding]
Oh my.
[man] There's an unexpected vibration.
- [woman] We need to get out quickly!
- [yells]
[woman 2] Ji-young! Hurry!
[crashing]
[yelling]
[silence]
- [alarm beeping]
- [Ji-young cries out]
- [explosion rumbles]
- [Ji-young yells]
[tense music playing]
[gasps]
[continues gasping]
- [watch ringing]
- Isn't that that woman?
[ringing stops]
[gasps]
Oh! [Gasps]
DR. JOO NAN-YOUNG SELECTED AS A MEMBER
OF THE FOURTH MARS EXPEDITION TEAM
[no audible dialogue]
[door opens]
Why are you sitting in the dark?
Why didn't you call me?
Oh, right, you did. I didn't answer.
Sorry, I was just swamped.
Oh, you tidied up. Thanks.
Jay?
When were you going to tell me?
Now.
When did you find out?
[Nan-young] A few days ago.
[scoffs]
Let me guess…
The night I was on stage?
Mm.
[Jay] You…
So this was your secret?
I'm sorry, Jay.
I had no choice.
[scoffs] We couldn't tell anyone.
Not even family.
Speaking of family,
does your father know
what you're about to do?
[scoffs] Even if I told him, he wouldn't...
Well, you should tell him anyway.
You should've told him in advance!
- Jay.
- [screen beeps]
Aren't you happy for me?
I've literally worked my whole life
for this.
- You know that.
- I know, of course.
At least I thought I did.
I guess maybe I convinced myself
that it wasn't what you wanted.
Yet, there I was,
blindly encouraging my girlfriend
to go running toward disaster?
Jay.
Stay with me.
[poignant music playing]
- You could die if you go.
- [Nan-young exhales]
[voice breaking] Don't do this, Jay.
Uh…
Did you go through my things?
Is that what you're focusing on right now?
I can't just watch you march
to your death.
What you saw was a worst-case scenario!
And that will never happen to me,
I promise!
You must think I'm an idiot 'cause clearly
you're gonna find a way to justify it.
This is why I couldn't tell you.
You're not at all like my father.
You want me to be like your dad?
Staring up at the sky,
sending messages into the void,
hoping she'll come back?
[breathes shakily]
All right then. I get it.
We should just end this.
[Jay exhales]
How…
How can you be so cruel?
[door closes]
[crying]
NAN-YOUNG'S
[continues crying]
♪ Even though ♪
♪ You were right beside me ♪
♪ I still missed you ♪
♪ Like you're not around… ♪
[Nan-young] Dad, I'm going to Mars.
Now I know how hard
this must have been for Mom.
I bet she's in orbit right about now.
[caregiver] Come on, sir.
Move away from the window.
♪ Count all the moons ♪
♪ Till we see each other again ♪
♪ I keep singing and singing ♪
♪ Though I know… ♪
[Nan-young] But you know
what the worst part is?
[announcement] The 2:45
American Airlines flight…
DELETE JAY'S NUMBER?
CONFIRM
[Nan-young] I finally understand Mom
for the first time.
Cruel irony.
[song fades]
[airplane taking off]
Hmm.
Huh?
[train rumbling]
[captain] We humans,
arguably the weakest life-form on Earth,
have fought, struggled,
and innovated for our survival.
We've discovered
new continents across the seas,
yet we've always dreamt of more.
[camera shutters clicking]
And now,
we seek to create
a space-faring civilization
beyond this blue planet.
The six-member crew standing here are
pioneers embarking on a great journey…
[camera shutters clicking]
[gasps]
[Rosa] Nans. You okay?
- Was it a nightmare?
- Huh?
- Mm-mm.
- [Rosa] You startled me.
[Nan-young sighs]
Sheesh, it smells like a locker room
in here, girl. Oh!
Let's get some air.
It's really beautiful outside!
Rosa, what are you…
Go on. Look. Ain't the weather handsome?
[Nan-young] Huh?
[sighs]
Oh.
Hmm.
[chuckles]
- [mom] All right, everyone! Grab a hand.
- [girl] Mommy.
- [mom] Watch your step.
- [girl] Are we finally ready?
[laughs] Jay, the tide!
[laughs]
[Jay exclaims]
[both laugh]
[Nan-young screams playfully]
[poignant music playing]
[Jay] Hey, Nan-young.
You have a pretty shitty boyfriend.
[Nan-young] You're just figuring that out?
[Jay] No style to speak of,
no money at all.
And not an inkling of patience,
which is why he's here.
I'm glad.
Makes me like you more.
- Imperfect Jay.
- [Jay chuckles]
You've got weird taste.
[Nan-young] And you?
Do you wish we'd never met?
No.
Not at all.
The best thing that's ever happened to me
was meeting you.
[laughs] Stop it, liar.
[Jay laughs] I mean it. Really.
If I'm being honest,
I'm still not fully on board.
It's hard for me to support this.
Make it home safe.
[music intensifies]
Come back to me.
I beg you.
[Nan-young] I'm sorry
for only thinking of myself.
[instruments beeping]
[NASA officer] Countdown T-minus ten.
- [Jay] For now, just think about yourself.
- [NASA officer] Seven. Six. Five…
[Jay] You have to be selfish for me
until you get back.
- [NASA officer] Two. One.
- [engines blasting]
- [Jay] Try not to do anything dangerous.
- [NASA officer] Zero.
[Jay] Protect yourself at all costs.
Promise me, Nan-young.
Tell me, above all, you'll be safe.
[Nan-young] I will.
I promise.
[rocket blasting]
[NASA officer] Lift-off confirmed.
The Seed-1 is slowly
lifting off the launchpad.
The engines are igniting beautifully.
Seed-1.
The first-stage separation in three,
two, one.
[grunts]
[music fades]
[crowd chattering]
- [NASA officer] Seed-I left Earth's orbit…
- Excuse me.
…and is heading toward Mars.
Finally, a great leap for mankind
is made once again.
[crowd cheering and clapping]
[man] Whoa! What a sight!
[Jay] Hmm.
[engines rumbling]
["Heart to Heart" playing]
[beeping]
[woman singing in Korean]
[inaudible]
[song continues]
[Jay] Nan-young, you've inspired me.
I want to move forward like you.
Both for myself
but also
for you too.
[song continues]
♪ You're from another world ♪
♪ I can feel, I can feel
Somewhere bigger than my star ♪
♪ Tell me your Sega
Name of your neighbor galaxy… ♪
[Jay] I finally finished it.
As my number one fan,
I thought that
you should hear my song first.
After all,
it's your opinion that matters most to me.
[Jay exhales]
[man] Hmm. It's good.
Guess the original songwriter
would know what's best.
- Ending's not half bad either.
- Di-a, let's set up a session.
- This'll be a great fit for the album.
- On one condition.
- Huh?
- And what's that?
I wanna sing it… live on stage.
[scoffs]
IT'S FINALLY DONE!
I WANTED YOU TO HEAR IT FIRST.
[man] I've finally found my true calling.
Farming!
[Nan-young] Mm.
Jay, it's me.
Our signal strength was good this morning.
So I rushed to the terminal
as fast as I could,
and your song
finally finished transferring.
- "['Bon Voyage" plays through headphones]
- ♪ I lose myself to fun… ♪
[Nan-young exhales softly]
You've finished it.
♪ Drifting to the unknown ♪
♪ Sleeping somewhere in between… ♪
[Nan-young sobs]
[poignant music playing]
All I could think about while I listened…
[sobbing continues]
…was how much I miss you…
[inaudible]
…and that I'm not there to console you.
That loneliness, it must be so painful.
I'm so sorry for that.
We'll be arriving on Mars soon,
which means we probably won't be able
to reach each other for a while.
But always remember, Jay,
out there in the starlight,
someone's cheering you on.
Your biggest fan.
[triumphant music playing]
[engines rumbling]
[music decreases in intensity]
[detector trilling]
[beep]
[music fades]
Stay strong, Jay.
[beep]
- Someone play some sweet music for us.
- [grunting]
[beep]
♪ I lose myself to fun… ♪
[man] That song? Again?
[groans] I left
my loved ones behind too, you know!
[Rosa] Leave 'em alone.
I'm just giving them a break
until they fix the antennas.
- [man] I know all the words to this song.
- [Rosa] Me too. [Grunts]
[detector trills]
Detected.
[Nan-young breathes heavily]
Object found.
[detector trilling]
[tense music playing]
Captain, Joo just found
the abandoned rover
from the second expedition.
Did she?
I'd like to get your permission
to retrieve the rover by myself.
Looks like that'll be
a two-hour round trip.
Yes. It's not far.
- Very well. Permission granted.
- Thank you, Captain.
Want me to come? I don't like the idea
of you going off alone.
[chuckles] Don't worry.
I'll be back before lunch.
Actually, would you mind heating up
my lunch kit too?
- I'm sure I'll be hungry.
- [Rosa] I'm already hungry. Don't be late.
[Nan-young] Yes, ma'am.
[wheels screeching]
[wind whistling]
[sighs]
Oh.
Uh…
- [sighs]
- [watch beeps]
Ah.
[door opens]
[Di-a] At it again, huh?
It's early. What do you want?
- This is your wake-up call for rehearsal.
- Yeah, yeah. I won't be late.
[sighs]
I found your in-ear monitors in my stuff.
[Di-a] Come on, Jay.
Try singing. In front of me.
[Jay sighs]
[engine whirring]
[Nan-young breathing heavily]
[inquisitive music playing]
The battery's dead.
[machinery whirring]
HQ, this is Joo.
Endurance rover seems stuck in the sand.
Requesting additional vehicle support.
- [radio static]
- HQ, do you copy?
[detector] Target.
[detector beeps] Life trace.
[trilling]
- HQ.
- [radio static]
HQ?
Suit, begin recording.
Comms are unstable.
Switching to log-based report.
Biomarkers have been detected
and are within 500 meters.
I'll examine the results
then head back to base.
[instruments playing]
- [man 1] Over here!
- [man 2] Sound check for drums first.
- [instruments playing]
- [crowd cheering]
[crowd chattering]
- [man 3] Di-a. In-ear monitors sound good?
- Uh, yeah, they sound good.
- [man 3] In-ears are good to go!
- But I think we can bump the vocals.
- [man 3] Turn up the vocals in her ears.
- [Jay] Hmm.
[mellow music playing]
- [Di-a] Jay!
- Huh?
[Di-a] Get with it!
That's where you're supposed to come in.
Oh, yeah.
- Sorry.
- [Di-a] This is our big chance.
Sorry, everyone.
Let's take it from the top.
[man] We'll go through
the rehearsal once more.
[engine revving]
[suit] Fifty meters ahead.
Crater cliff. Be aware.
[tense music playing]
[Nan-young] A meteor impact seems
to have exposed an underground lava cave.
[breathing heavily]
[detector trills]
- Tracing route.
- [Nan-young] Huh?
[whirring]
- [detector] Route found.
- [Nan-young exhales sharply]
[exhales]
[grunts]
[grunting, heavy breathing]
Captain, a tornado signal
has been detected
in the eastern part of the Arcadia Plains.
[captain] We had a briefing
about this last night.
[man] The EF strength has been rapidly
and aggressively growing
for the last hour.
Any exterior work in those regions
will likely be too risky
until tomorrow afternoon.
[captain] That shouldn't present
any problems. Wait.
Captain, have you looked outside?
Rosa, where's Nan-young?
I've been trying
to establish communication,
but nothing so far.
- [captain] Damn it!
- Ugh!
[wind gusting]
[Rosa] It looks worse than it is.
Right?
♪ Bet you know
All the words to shut me up  ♪
♪ Throw my heart out  ♪
[captain] This is HQ.
[breaking up] Nan-young… read me?
- [Rosa] Stand by…
- This is Joo. Do you copy?
[Rosa breaking up on radio] Joo… copy?
I don't think she can hear us.
What… what do we do?
The tornado is heading your way!
[wind roaring]
[detector] Tracing route.
Suit, begin recording.
I'm entering an unidentified cave
where there are traces of the bio marker.
[coughs] Radio reception remains weak.
This recording will serve as my report...
[screams]
[wind whistling]
[metal creaking]
[rope whipping]
- [crash]
- [Nan-young cries out]
- [rope whipping]
- [creaking]
[screams, moans]
[gasps, cries out]
[tense music playing]
♪ I'll let you break my heart…  ♪
[high-pitched squealing]
[wind roaring]
[panting]
[creaking]
[breathing]
[beeping]
[creaking]
[ominous music playing]
[music builds]
[string snaps]
[crash]
[wind roaring]
[Di-a] I wrote that last song
when I had a devastating crush.
- [chuckles]
- [crowd chanting] Di-a! Di-a!
- That one is called "Moonlight."
- [crowd continues chanting]
[tense music playing]
- [Nan-young breathes]
- [alarm beeping]
[regular breathing continues]
[music builds, stops]
- [suit] Alert. Helmet damaged.
- [Nan-young cries out]
[suit] Oxygen leak detected.
[panting]
[suit] Oxygen level, 10.5.
- 10.1.
- [groans]
- 9.6.
- [grunting]
- Alert. Helmet damaged.
- [air hissing]
- Oxygen leak detected.
- [exclaims]
- Alert.
- [hissing stops]
[trilling and beeping]
[panting]
[grunts]
[detector] Life trace.
Route found.
[Nan-young coughing]
[detector] Tracing route.
[Nan-young grunting]
[cries out]
[Rosa] Rover, start engine.
Open hatch! [Pants]
Oh no. It seems like
there's an electrical interference
with the motion sensor.
[captain] Damn storm.
- [man] We got something from Nan-young.
- Pull it up on the screen.
Remaining oxygen is 9.1?
She can't breathe
because of the air bleeding.
[panting]
[grunts]
We need to go in right now. [Grunts]
Check Nan-young's last words video.
Monitor for any confidential information.
Captain, we can't.
If we don't something now, she'll die!
She only has ten minutes of air left.
The origin point of the signal
is two hours from here.
[Rosa] So what? She's not dead yet.
We still have ten more minutes!
[panicked cries] Captain!
[detector trilling]
- [suit] Battery power at 15%.
- [Nan-young grunting]
[suit] Oxygen level at risk.
- Activating survival mode.
- [Nan-young cries out]
[suit] Reducing battery power.
Warning.
Suit oxygen level at 8%.
Carbon dioxide filtration…
- [panicked panting]
- [beeping]
[Di-a] Ah!
Thank you for coming out to the showcase
performance of The Moles.
One last surprise for all the fans
who made the trek to come see us here.
[crowd cheering]
Jay!
- [crowd chanting] Jay! Jay! Jay! Jay!
- [clears throat]
[crowd continues chanting]
Jay! Jay! Jay! Jay! Jay! Jay!
[wind whistling]
[sniffling, whimpers]
[sobbing]
Jay. It's me,
Nan-young.
- [beeping]
- [breathing heavily]
When I was a kid,
I never remembered to carry
an umbrella with me.
[rain pattering]
[poignant music playing]
All the same,
I never seemed to get rained on.
Dad would always come
to pick me up from school.
He was always staring up at the sky.
I guess that gave him a knack
for predicting the weather.
I kept that habit into adulthood.
I almost never carry an umbrella with me.
- [horn honks]
- Ah!
- [Jay] Oh.
- [Nan-young] But you know what?
[Jay breathes heavily]
- [Nan-young] On that day, you know.
- Nan-young.
[Nan-young] The day you started calling me
by my name. Well, that was…
[Jay] I can… call you
by your name now, right?
[Nan-young] It was the first time that
I shared an umbrella since I was a kid.
[laughing]
I'm pretty sure
it's also the day that I fell for you.
[panting]
Hmm.
If you're watching this right now,
then it's not good news.
I imagine it's not pleasant.
I'm sorry.
[Nan-young panting in suit]
Jay,
I clung to my path in life so tight.
But then I stumbled down a side road,
a road I didn't expect at all,
and found there a glittering oasis.
[Nan-young grunting in suit]
That's who you are to me, Jay.
A guide who led me down a road
I didn't even know existed.
[Nan-young gasping in suit]
I can't imagine how difficult this is.
But, Jay…
Please, try not to be too sad
and try to move on.
Live without regrets. Be true to yourself.
[gasping]
And please, use that voice of yours.
And have a beautiful life.
[breathing shakily]
[gasping softly]
[exhales]
I've never seen Jay sing.
Okay, switch to camera three.
Let's get the wide shot.
- [man] Can we get a check on mic one?
- [Nan-young] And don't forget, Jay.
Somewhere in the starlight…
[laughing]
…there's someone who's forever and always…
…cheering you on.
[Jay clears throat]
[singing a cappella]
♪ I lose myself to fun  ♪
♪ In nameless cities ♪
♪ Drifting to the unknown ♪
♪ Sleeping somewhere in between  ♪
♪ For someone like me
Life is sometimes just hard to foresee  ♪
♪ Holding my breath
I'll step through concrete mountains  ♪
♪ I'll overcome it all
And wipe the dust off my face ♪
♪ Many people are caught
Within a question  ♪
♪ In between zero and one is where ♪
♪ They meet their love ♪
♪ Beyond the stars  ♪
♪ Have a good ride, bon voyage  ♪
♪ Time doesn't matter  ♪
♪ We're meant for each other  ♪
♪ Although we're far apart  ♪
♪ I'll always find a way to your heart…  ♪
[man] Hey! [Laughs]
- [Di-a] Hey.
- Enough! Enough already.
Come on, you guys. I mean, that was
absolutely one of our best shows,
hands down!
["Bon Voyage" continues]
[Jay vocalizing]
Breaking news.
NASA has reported that
the Korean national Dr. Joo Nan-young,
who embarked on a Mars expedition
in November, has gone missing.
It appears a sudden shift in weather
severed communication lines,
and Dr. Joo's location has remained
untraceable for over an hour.
♪ You can lean on me
And always hold me tight… ♪
[sighs]
Did she remember her umbrella?
NASA reports that Dr. Joo went missing
while engaging in an exploratory mission
of an unidentified lava cave…
[groans] No! It can't be! No!
[reporter] NASA continues to…
♪ Reach my hand out ♪
♪ And your radiance shines on throughout  ♪
♪ I'll call your name over and over  ♪
- ♪ As loud as I can shout  ♪
- [horn honking]
♪ Now I'm down here
Looking way up to the sky  ♪
♪ Singing to the stars so that
We both can live on as time goes by ♪
[gasping]
♪ Beyond the stars ♪
- ♪ Have a good ride, bon voyage ♪
- Jay.
[sobbing] I'm scared.
♪ Time doesn't matter ♪
♪ We're meant for each other ♪
♪ Although we're far apart ♪
♪ I'll always find a way to your heart… ♪
I need to see Mr. Joo, your patient.
It's about his daughter!
[Jay grunts]
- [security] Hey.
- [nurse] Wait!
[Jay grunts, pants]
Mr. Joo!
- Can I… borrow this for a while?
- Why?
What is it, son?
Maybe you also have a message to send?
[Jay] Yeah.
[Jay vocalizing]
[Nan-young gasping]
[grunting]
["Bon Voyage" ends]
[gasping]
Mommy! [Giggles]
Nan-young! [Laughs]
- [Jay] Nan-young.
- There you are.
[Jay] All I ever wanted
was to surround you with light.
[father] What should we have for dinner?
[Ji-young] I don't know.
Maybe we do ramyeon?
[father] Ramyeon again?
[Jay] The last thing I wanted you to see
were the shadows I carry inside.
How could a nobody like me
ever dare to want someone
as extraordinary as you?
I'd tell myself that
I should just put an end to it.
But in the morning,
I'd long for those traces of you.
And in the end, it was you who taught me
that light and shadow are inseparable.
And if you don't embrace the shadows,
then you'll never see the light.
- [thunder crashing]
- Please! Please work!
Just waiting indefinitely,
I won't lie, it hurts.
Sometimes a lot.
But if there's one thing I know,
it's that I can't ever give up on you!
So don't you dare go giving up on me.
[Nan-young inhales]
[Jay] I need you to come back.
Put an end to this wait
and save me.
[gasps]
[gasping]
♪ Beyond the stars ♪
♪ Have a good ride, bon voyage ♪
- ♪ Time doesn't matter ♪
- Jay!
[Jay] Sorry for the wait.
♪ We're meant for each other ♪
♪ Although we're far apart ♪
♪ I'll always find a way to your heart… ♪
[Jay] Crybaby.
[Nan-young] I'm not. I'm not crying.
Neither am I.
[Nan-young sobbing]
Oh no.
Please don't! Jay! Don't go!
[whimpering]
Don't do this! You can't!
Please don't leave me, Jay! [Cries]
No!
I'm begging you! Don't leave me, Jay!
[sobbing] Jay, please.
[song ends]
[beeping]
[panting]
[breathing heavily]
- [grunting]
- [metal squealing]
[grunting]
[metal bangs]
[panting]
[suit] Main system operating nominally.
Manual mode activated.
- [sighs]
- [faint beeping]
[poignant music playing]
[beeping continues]
[sighs]
[beeping fades]
[silence]
[Nan-young] It's warm.
[breathing faintly]
[ethereal music playing]
- [grunts]
- [tapping on glass]
[Nan-young exhales]
[inaudible]
[grunting]
Mom?
I love you.
[cries quietly]
[Nan-young crying softly]
- [Nan-young] I made it!
- Oh!
- Nan… Nan-young.
- [Nan-young sobbing]
Nan-young! Nan-young! Oh!
[Nan-young] And also…
- Nan-young, where are you?
- [Nan-young] I'm alive.
Can you hear me? Oh.
[Nan-young] I heard your message.
[laughs]
Your voice sounded so unfamiliar.
Are you Jay? [Laughs]
[Jay exhales]
[Nan-young] Maybe it's the distance,
but it feels like a dream.
[Jay chuckles]
It's not a dream. Thank goodness.
[Nan-young] I've come all this way,
and only now I've realized,
well,
there's something
I've been meaning to tell you,
and I'm ready now.
I love you, Jay.
[Jay chuckles]
[both laugh]
[Rosa] Nan-young!
Thank goodness.
It's you. It's you! I've found you.
Over here! She's alive! Oh my goodness!
[journalist] Hello, everyone,
and welcome to Today in History.
On this day, Koreans and all the people
of the world were awestruck.
Not only did the survival
and dramatic rescue of Dr. Joo Nan-young
hold the world rapt,
but even more sensational
was the fact that Dr. Joo discovered
a cultivated garden of Amur Adonis flowers
beneath the martian surface.
[Nan-young] There are certain things
that you can only realize
from a great distance.
Something I'd failed to notice
before I went away.
[panting]
Now that I'm back, I treasure it.
[Nan-young] To think
it had always been right here.
Beneath my feet.
[emotional music playing]
Before my eyes.
Within us.
[exhales]
And even better,
it's right here
on this planet.
["Take Me" playing]
♪ Take me to another star ♪
[singing in Korean]
LOST IN STARLIGHT
[vocalizing]
[singing in Korean]
♪ Oh, take me to another star ♪
♪ Take me to another star ♪
[singing in Korean]
- [song ends]
- [whirring]
["Bon Voyage" playing in Korean]
[song fades]